The target has appeared.
目标已经出现。
Can shoot.
可以射击。
Wait.
等待。
It's not like the woman came to cooperate,
这女人又不是来配合的，
clearly knew there was danger, why didn't he leave?
明明知道有危险，为什么还不走？
If I retreat, you won't be able to retreat.
我退了，你就退不了了。
Several snipers,
几个狙击手，
currently can only confirm one.
目前只能确认一项。
Understand.
理解。
People from which side.
哪边的人。
Military power or Japan?
军事实力还是日本？
At this time it is still unclear.
目前还不清楚。
However, you have already entered the range,
然而，你已经进入了范围，
it's been some time
已经有一段时间了
but he never fired.
但他从未开枪。
He definitely knows
他绝对知道
today you will work together with the boss here,
今天你将和这里的老板一起工作，
Want to catch us all at once.
想一下子抓住我们所有人。
But they are confused.
但他们很困惑。
Because there are no superiors and subordinates.
因为没有上级和下级之分。
Will meet like us.
会像我们一样相遇。
We look like we're on a date.
我们看起来像是在约会。
Or cheating.
或者作弊。
Up to them.
由他们决定。
But they were already suspicious
但他们已经产生了怀疑
to information.
信息。
But I'm afraid this suspicion is only temporary.
但这种怀疑恐怕只是暂时的。
Correct.
正确的。
So we must immediately think of a solution.
所以我们必须立即想办法解决。
Time and place
时间和地点
the place is not wrong.
这个地方没有错。
Team leader Tao,
陶组长，
will shoot or not
会不会开枪
our goal is to get rid of
我们的目标是摆脱
and his superiors.
和他的上级。
If shot now
如果现在开枪的话
will surprise the real target
会让真正的目标大吃一惊
I really didn't think about it
我真的没想到
you are a parrot
你是一只鹦鹉
I didn't think so before either
我之前也不这么认为
Plum blossom Four is you.
梅花四就是你。
So you already knew my identity from the start?
所以你从一开始就已经知道我的身份了？
Fourth Comrade Meihua.
四是梅花同志。
Tell me about the current situation.
说说目前的情况吧。
You've heard about business problems, right?
您听说过业务问题，对吧？
I don't have an identity as a cover
我没有身份作为掩护
Shan Xia also got the medicine formula
山霞也拿到了药方
I failed the organization's trust in me.
我辜负了组织对我的信任。
Initial organizational plan
初步组织计划
to tell you to leave Shanghai.
告诉你离开上海。
I once saw Lao Lu writing a work report
我曾经看到老鲁在写工作报告
your work report.
你的工作报告。
I assumed you wouldn't agree to go.
我以为你不会同意去
So, I've asked permission from the organization.
所以，我已经请求了组织的许可。
But now
但现在
now I also have no other way.
现在我也没有别的办法了。
There is one clue
有一个线索
do you know Xindi?
你知道新地吗？
Xindi?
Xindi?
I heard the conversation between the foot of the mountain and Neta.
我听到了山脚下和内塔的对话。
Yamashita said,
山下说，
we look forward to the opening of the second phase of the Shan Project
期待山项目二期的开业
is in Xindi.
就在新地。
Unfortunately, after that I was interrupted.
不幸的是，之后我就被打断了。
I didn't hear the rest of the story.
我没有听到故事的其余部分。
What is that new place
那个新地方是什么
is a place name?
是地名吗？
I've checked it.
我已经查过了。
Shanghai is no new place.
上海并不是一个新地方。
What's that?
那是什么？
Must be checked clearly.
一定要检查清楚。
However, the most important thing now,
不过，现在最重要的是，
must be free from here
必须从这里自由
what in the box is copper plate?
盒子里是什么铜板？
As long as you hand over the box to me,
只要你把盒子交给我
then it is clear that I am your superior,
那么很明显我是你的上级，
they will shoot.
他们会开枪。
We can't hand over the copper plates now,
我们现在不能交出铜板，
also can't act rashly.
也不能轻举妄动。
Correct.
正确的。
Their main goal is copper.
他们的主要目标是铜。
Then kill us all.
然后杀掉我们所有人。
Because now I can't confirm my identity
因为现在我无法确认我的身份
so they still doubt
所以他们仍然怀疑
but if
但如果
if there's anything we want to leave behind,
如果有什么我们想留下的
they won't care too much.
他们不会太在意。
Will shoot straight away.
会直接开枪。
You're at three o'clock
你现在是三点钟
is the Su Zhou river.
是苏州河。
As long as we can jump into the river,
只要我们能跳进河里，
we'll stay out of range of snipers
我们将远离狙击手的射程
You mean, I took the box and ran to the river embankment?
你的意思是，我拿着箱子跑到河堤上去了？
Can't.
不能。
As soon as you touch the box,
当你触碰盒子的那一刻，
they will shoot you,
他们会向你开枪，
I have one way.
我有一个办法。
What way?
有什么办法？
Did you kiss me?
你吻我了吗？
Don't dare anymore?
不敢了吗？
It seems,
它似乎，
This woman did not come to work together.
这个女人不是来一起工作的。
Target Chen Jia Ping.
目标陈家平。
Why are you angry with me?
你为什么生我的气？
They want to run away
他们想逃跑
shot Chen Jia Ping
shot Chen Jia Ping
Aim for that woman
瞄准那个女人
block their escape route.
堵住他们的逃路。
Don't kill me.
别杀我。
My son is only two months old.
我儿子才两个月大。
Please save us.
请拯救我们。
Running backwards is dangerous.
向后跑很危险。
How are you?
你好吗？
Lu Fang
Lu Fang
protect me!
保护我！
Jia Ping
Jia Ping
It turns out that Chen Jia Ping's boss is you
原来陈家平的老板就是你
It turns out you were the one who betrayed Chen Jia Ping.
原来背叛陈家平的人就是你。
Chen Jia Ping dimana?
Chen Jia Ping dimana?
I don't know
我不知道
what happened to him
他发生了什么事情
don't you know?
你不知道吗？
Is he still alive?
他还活着吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I only know he's here to help me,
我只知道他是来帮助我的
actually you really love him
其实你真的很爱他
Is that true?
真的吗？
I should be the one asking you this.
我应该是问你这个问题的人。
Do you really love him
你真的爱他吗
I love her.
我爱她。
But I have to kill him
但我必须杀了他
in here is the copper edition.
这是铜版。
Your evil plan will not work.
你的邪恶计划不会得逞。
You won't be able to run away from this either
你也无法逃避这个
sooner or later, your crimes
迟早，你的罪行
Of course.
当然。
Everyone retreat!
所有人都撤退！
Defeat
打败
defeated!
败了！
Possible!
可能的！
Well, look no further.
好吧，别再看了。
Back off, back off.
退后，退后。
Go back.
回去。
Just leave.
走吧。
Left twin.
左边双胞胎。
Already home.
已经到家了。
I'm not dead.
我还没死。
You're very disappointed, right?
你很失望，对吧？
You die, I'm more disappointed.
你死了，我更失望。
At least you didn't deny it.
至少你没有否认。
Just like a top secret military agent should do.
就像一名绝密军事特工应该做的那样。
Tao Dachun definitely wouldn't understand.
陶大春肯定听不懂。
He's tried hard
他已经很努力了
prepare an ambush
准备伏击
but still can't get rid of you.
但还是无法摆脱你。
Why do that to me?
为什么要这样对我？
You betrayed me.
你背叛了我。
Betraying the trust you built again.
再次背叛你建立的信任。
This has nothing to do with my beliefs.
这与我的信仰无关。
So what does it have to do with it?
那么这有什么关系呢？
You killed Captain Liu.
你杀了刘队长。
I must take revenge for him!
我一定要为他报仇！
Liu Wuchang is dead.
刘无常死了。
Why?
为什么？
Still don't dare to confess?
还是不敢表白？
This isn't like you.
这不像你。
He helped me.
他帮助了我。
Why should I kill him?
我为什么要杀他？
That's why your sins are even more unforgivable.
所以你的罪孽就更加不可饶恕了。
I didn't kill him.
我没有杀他。
I didn't kill Liu Wuchang.
我没有杀刘无常。
The person who killed him,
杀了他的人，
it must be because he instigated our relationship,
一定是因为他挑起了我们的关系，
and incited you to betray and kill me.
并煽动你背叛并杀死我。
So it turns out.
事实证明。
You killed Lu Fang
你杀了吕方
Lu Fang is dead
吕方死了
weren't you the one who killed him?
杀他的人不是你吗？
Team leader Tao.
队长陶.
I've got the copper plate.
我有铜板。
Good work.
干得好。
Dimana Chen Jia Ping?
Dimana Chen Jia Ping?
Is dead
死了
are you sure?
你确定吗？
If he doesn't die,
如果他不死的话
I will find it too
我也会找到
and killed him with my own hands
并亲手杀了他
Good.
好的。
What about this woman?
这个女人呢？
Already injured.
已经受伤了。
I will take him away
我会带他走
Why
为什么
I don't want him to die so soon.
我不想让他这么快死。
It turns out you already knew from the start
原来你从一开始就已经知道了
she had an affair with Chen Jia Ping
她与陈家平有染
Good
好的
I'll leave him to you.
我把他留给你了。
Resolving old and new grudges together.
新旧恩怨一起化解。
Copper version?
铜版？
Finally back in your hands.
终于又回到了你的手中。
So what was in the box then?
那么当时盒子里装的是什么？
You don't need to care.
你不需要关心。
I've replaced it with something else
我已经用别的东西替换了它
Why?
为什么？
Why betray us in the first place
为什么一开始就背叛我们
now you want to help us?
现在你想帮助我们吗？
Suddenly I understood one thing
突然我明白了一件事
Chen Jia Ping and I have personal grievances
我和陈家平有私人恩怨
I cannot be taken advantage of by people with evil intentions
我不能被不怀好意的人利用
I believe that the Communist Party is justice
我相信共产党是正义的
believes that the Communist Party can bring hope to China
相信共产党能给中国带来希望
so I won't let the military get the silver version.
所以我不会让军队得到银色版本。
Will not let their evil plans succeed.
不会让他们的邪恶计划得逞。
You get off here
你在这里下车
make sure to take the copper plate back to the border area
确保将铜板带回边界区域
Thank You.
谢谢。
Colleague.
同事。
So what's your next plan?
那么你的下一步计划是什么？
Don't know.
不知道。
I have no other way anymore.
我已经没有别的办法了。
Also there is nowhere to go
也无处可去
why do you prefer this dead end
你为什么喜欢这个死胡同
rather than believe that Jia Ping had been framed?
而不是相信家平是被陷害的？
I rather believe what I see
我宁愿相信我所看到的
Jia Ping must still be alive
家平肯定还活着
the truth will be revealed someday
总有一天真相会被揭露
I also hope he lives
我也希望他能活着
he should have died in my hands
他应该死在我手里
after that, Lu Fang got out of the car
随后，吕方下了车。
what happened again
又发生了什么事
I wouldn't know.
我不知道。
It seems I misunderstood you.
看来我误会你了。
I also misunderstood you.
我也误会你了。
It's broken even.
已经收支平衡了
My wife,
我的妻子，
Remember what I said at the wedding?
还记得我在婚礼上说过的话吗？
You're not perfect
你并不完美
I'm not perfect either
我也不完美
however, if we combine,
然而，如果我们结合起来，
it's perfect.
这是完美的。
But now,
但现在，
not so perfect.
不是那么完美。
Do you still remember?
你还记得吗？
where we first met?
我们第一次见面是在哪里？
Who's that?
那是谁？
Don't.
不。
Three, two, one.
三二一。
Lame!
瘸！
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Think about why soy milk should be mixed with cakwe.
想想为什么豆浆要和cakwe混合。
You can also add eggs.
您还可以添加鸡蛋。
What is it?
它是什么？
It doesn't matter
没关系
the egg fell.
鸡蛋掉下来了。
Can add eggs
可以加鸡蛋吗
kill people
杀人
Hurry up
赶快
to kill me,
杀了我，
insert yourself into,
将自己置入，
tuan Shan Xia.
tuan Shan Xia.
Plum blossom four and red peach blossom five are dead.
梅花四、红桃花五都死了。
Are you sure?
你确定吗？
I saw it myself.
我亲眼所见。
As expected.
正如预期的那样。
It turns out they killed each other.
原来他们互相残杀了。
Finally die together
最后一起死
qian Xiu Cai
qian Xiu Cai
You didn't just help me find Lu Fang
你不只是帮我找到了吕方
this hidden pkc
这个隐藏的pkc
have found used copper coins
发现用过的铜币
Now
现在
You also helped me defeat plum blossom four and red peach blossom five.
你还帮我打败了梅花四和红桃花五。
You're very talented.
你很有才华。
I really admire him
我真的很佩服他
Thank you Mr. Shan Xia.
Thank you Mr. Shan Xia.
It seems like
这好像是
Taihe commercial bank manager position
太和商业银行经理职务
is yours.
是你的。
It's you
是你
Qian Xiu locked you up here
千修把你锁在这里
so you too
所以你也是
memberitahu Qian Xiu Cai
memberitahu Qian Xiu Cai
My and Shuang Tao's identities
我和双桃的身份
why did you kill Captain Liu?
为什么要杀刘队长？
I didn't kill.
我没有杀人。
Isn't it Chen Jia Ping?
不是陈家平吗？
Bukan Chen Jia Ping
Bukan Chen Jia Ping
Who
WHO
what do you want to say?
你想说什么？
Director Jiang.
Director Jiang.
Why did he do that?
他为什么那样做？
Captain Liu is a traitor.
刘队长是叛徒。
Stand up and stand tall.
站起来，站得高高的。
Our beliefs have reached the communist side
我们的信仰已经到达了共产主义一边
bagaimana Jiang Zhaoguo tahu?
bagaimana Jiang Zhaoguo tahu?
I said it.
我说了。
So, Jiang Zhaoguo was also the one who told you to lie
所以，蒋兆国也是让你撒谎的人
harm Chen Jia Ping.
害陈家平。
Is it true
是真的吗
if I don't do it,
如果我不这样做
ketua Jiang akan membunuh Zhou Qingfang
ketua Jiang akan membunuh Zhou Qingfang
so Qian Xiu killed Lu Fang
so Qian Xiu killed Lu Fang
and blamed Zuo Shuang Tao.
and blamed Zuo Shuang Tao.
Right?
正确的？
Qian Xiu Cai
Qian Xiu Cai
is a demon
是一个恶魔
also a talented person
也是一个有才华的人
he did many things to be proud of
他做了很多值得骄傲的事情
but no one told him.
但没有人告诉他。
He kept looking for me to talk
他一直找我说话
I know everything.
我知道所有的东西。
And agree to one of my requests.
并同意我的一项要求。
I will tell you.
我会告诉你。
What conditions?
什么条件？
Let go.
松手。
What about Captain Liu's letter?
刘队长的信呢？
Captain Liu Quotes
刘队长语录
is me.
是我。
Forged.
锻造的。
I've studied handwriting
我学过书法
and very expert in
并且非常擅长
where was that letter before?
那封信之前在哪里？
Director Jiang burned the letter.
江主任把信烧了。
What's in the letter?
信里写了什么？
Tell me.
告诉我。
Captain Liu said,
刘队长说，
I hope you can follow the faith
希望你能追随信仰
and your dreams.
和你的梦想。
At the end of the letter,
在信的最后，
he gave you a poem.
他给了你一首诗。
Don't hear the sound of leaves breaking through the forest
听不到树叶冲破森林的声音
Why not shout and keep moving
为什么不喊叫并继续前进
Your wounds are very serious.
你的伤很严重。
Can't live much longer.
活不了多久了。
I know
我知道
Your stab today almost killed me.
你今天的一刀差点杀了我。
Which puncture?
哪个穿刺？
That stab
那一刺
aren't you avoiding it?
你不是在逃避吗？
If I don't run away,
如果我不逃跑的话
won't you be a widow?
你不会成为寡妇吗？
I'm sure you'll avoid it.
我相信你会避免它。
Oh God.
天啊。
Too scary.
太可怕了。
How did you know?
你怎么知道？
While I'm waiting for you at home,
当我在家里等你的时候
keep thinking
继续思考
things that have happened,
已经发生的事情，
I'm just thinking
我只是在想
Open the window to breathe fresh air.
打开窗户呼吸新鲜空气。
Then I saw
然后我看到
opposite is the reflection from the telescope.
相反的是望远镜的反射。
Suddenly I understood
突然我明白了
this is not as simple as I thought
这并不像我想象的那么简单
I was too stupid before.
以前我太傻了。
Of course.
当然。
I went to find Hu Jun.
我去找胡军了。
He has also confessed.
他也承认了。
Still can.
还是可以的
Not that stupid.
没那么傻。
How about you?
你呢？
I am...
我是...
I see
我懂了
I saw the knife stuck in Lu Fang's body
我看到吕方身上插着刀
honestly a second
老实说一秒钟
I did suspect you.
我确实怀疑过你。
But after I thought carefully
但我仔细想了想
even if you really kill Lu Fang
就算你真的杀了吕方
You wouldn't be so stupid as to leave the knife at the scene, right?
你不会傻到把刀留在现场吧？
When I came home, I saw you carrying a knife
当我回到家时，我看到你拿着刀
peeling apples.
削苹果皮。
I'm certain
我确定
The person who killed Lu Fang wasn't you.
杀死吕方的人不是你。
You didn't realize it anyway?
反正你也没意识到？
It's too quiet around our house
我们家周围太安静了
silence that never existed.
从未存在过的沉默。
This means that from the start there were people organizing the defense.
这意味着从一开始就有人组织防御。
do you know
你知道吗
actually,
实际上，
when you say we're not perfect at this point,
当你说我们目前还不完美时
I already understand what you mean.
我已经明白你的意思了。
However there are a few things
不过有几点
which cannot be said directly.
这不能直接说。
What if there are eavesdroppers?
如果有窃听者怎么办？
Compact?
袖珍的？
Satu Qian Xiu Cai
Satu Qian Xiu Cai
one country of Zhao
赵国一国
create your own tactics
创建自己的战术
to incite us both
煽动我们俩
to kill each other.
互相残杀。
Fortunately,
幸运的是，
we choose to trust each other
我们选择互相信任
but now it's still not perfect
但现在它仍然不完美
under the mountain.
山下。
Sell, sell.
卖，卖。
Movie star Han Lu marries a rich Japanese merchant,
影星韩露嫁给日本富商，
The wedding party will be held soon.
婚宴即将举行。
I suddenly want to drink coffee.
我突然想喝咖啡。
You just wait for me in the car.
你就在车里等我吧。
Good.
好的。
If you really marry Takeshi Yamashita,...
如果你真的嫁给了山下武的话……
You will become a notorious traitor.
你将成为臭名昭著的叛徒。
You will forever be nailed to the pillar of shame.
你将永远被钉在耻辱柱上。
Do you know?
你知道吗？
I always disappoint you,
我总是让你失望
makes you hurt,
让你受伤，
It's because I endured too much
是因为我承受了太多
I carry too much burden.
我背负着太多的负担。
Now it's different.
现在情况不同了。
Now the mission is a complete failure.
现在任务彻底失败了。
I also have no face to return to Chongqing.
我也没有脸回重庆了。
In my life,
在我生命中，
now you are the only one.
现在你是唯一的一个。
Which makes us forget everything.
这让我们忘记了一切。
Looking for a place where no one knows us,
寻找一个没人认识我们的地方，
and start a new life.
并开始新的生活。
Good?
好的？
This is a plane ticket to Hong Kong.
这是飞往香港的机票。
I will be waiting for you.
我会等着你。
Always waiting for you.
永远等着你。
Friends
朋友们
it's time for battle.
战斗时间到了。
Welcome to join our fight.
欢迎加入我们的战斗。
This is Gao Fang.
这是高芳。
He intercepted important information with the radio.
他用无线电截获了重要信息。
Dear friends,
亲爱的朋友们，
we have been misled before.
我们以前被误导过。
A new place is not a place
新地方不是一个地方
but rather a film that preaches military doctrine.
而是一部宣扬军事学说的电影。
The name of this film is Xindi
这部电影的名字叫新地
Apart from that, this film
除此之外，这部电影
will be released soon at Luhua cinemas.
即将在鲁花院线上映。
I've also targeted
我也瞄准了
the counterfeit money factory is in the underground of the Lu Hua cinema.
假币工厂在鲁华电影院地下。
Tomorrow at two o'clock in the afternoon,
明天下午两点，
karasuno dan Hanlu
乌野丹汉路
residence at the foot of Shanghai mountain.
住处上海山脚下。
Will hold a traditional Japanese wedding ceremony.
将举行传统的日本婚礼。
After that, they would go to Lu Hua cinema
之后，他们就去鲁花电影院
to hold an open wedding party.
举办一场公开的婚礼。
After dinner,
晚饭后，
team commander Hata Junliu from Shanghai
来自上海的队长畑俊柳
will arrive at the location.
将会到达该地点。
Signed a film investment agreement with Yamashita.
与山下签订电影投资协议。
Film investment is a cover.
电影投资只是一个幌子。
The essence of this agreement...
该协议的实质...
Regarding the launch of the second phase of the Shan Project.
关于启动掸邦项目二期工程。
So our target this time,
所以我们这次的目标，
save workers and members
拯救工人和会员
and experts.
和专家。
Then, it will output
然后，它会输出
minted coins,
铸造的硬币，
and printing equipment.
和印刷设备。
Destroy
破坏
however, there are actually still two major difficulties
但实际上仍然存在两大困难
which cannot be solved.
这是无法解决的。
The underground counterfeit money factory is divided into two areas,
地下假币工厂分为两个区域，
factory,
工厂，
member workspace.
成员工作区。
There is a wall-shaped safe
有一个墙壁形状的保险箱
we go through the explosion
我们经历爆炸
we can enter the worker's printing place,
我们可以进入工人的打印地点，
while expert studios...
而专家工作室...
There is an iron door five centimeters thick
有一扇五厘米厚的铁门
can it explode?
它能爆炸吗？
Want to blow up this iron gate,
想要炸毁这扇铁门，
it would take at least ten kilograms
至少需要十公斤
up to ten kilograms
重达十公斤
even if we blow up the iron gate
即使我们炸毁铁门
under the influence of strong air flow
在强烈气流的影响下
the people inside had no chance of surviving
里面的人没有生还的机会
the only way
唯一的办法
is to take the lock of the iron door.
就是拿铁门的锁。
But the key is in the hands of the foot of the mountain.
但钥匙却在山脚下。
Good.
好的。
Tuan Shan Xia.
Tuan Shan Xia.
Because the country of Zhao no longer had any value
因为赵国已经没有任何价值了
I don't understand.
我不明白。
Why do you want to marry Han Lu?
为什么要嫁给韩露？
Now I need it
现在我需要它
Chinese film star.
中国电影明星。
Specialized in making films with the spirit of the Japanese empire
专门制作具有日本帝国精神的电影
useful for paralyzing the Chinese mind
对于麻痹中国人的思想有用
I understand.
我明白。
There's one thing
有一点
I'm just telling you.
我只是告诉你。
What is it?
它是什么？
I like.
我喜欢。
Leaving
离开
on Han Lu's body.
韩璐的身上。
It turns out
事实证明
scars can make a woman
伤疤可以让女人
a woman.
一个女人。
Kimono has no pockets
和服没有口袋
always carry important items,
总是携带重要物品，
usually put in Xin Xuan's pocket.
一般都放在辛轩的口袋里。
Small seeds.
小种子。
Later at 4 o'clock
稍后4点
We must complete tasks on time
我们必须按时完成任务
after completing today's tasks,
完成今天的任务后，
we will leave Shanghai.
我们将离开上海。
I will take you back to my hometown.
我会带你回我的家乡。
Where is my hometown?
我的家乡在哪里？
In the beautiful Sungai Panas.
在美丽的Sungai Panas。
My hometown is very beautiful.
我的家乡非常美丽。
Meadow
草地
there is a lake
有一个湖
the grass there is most fertile.
那里的草最肥沃。
The water there is the sweetest.
那里的水是最甜的。
You can eat until you are full every day.
每天都可以吃到饱为止。
And drink until it's full.
然后喝到喝饱为止。
Then keep running, keep running.
然后继续跑，继续跑。
Keep running until the moon rises
继续奔跑直到月亮升起
the meadow will be very peaceful.
草地将会非常平静。
I can take you to eat roast mutton
我可以带你去吃烤羊肉
Correct.
正确的。
You don't eat meat
你不吃肉
you just like eating grass.
你就是喜欢吃草。
I've been careless these past few years,
这几年我太不小心了
maybe work for Japanese people.
也许对日本人有用。
Almost made a big mistake
差点犯下大错
so I want to sit in the village meadow
所以我想坐在村子的草地上
see the moon in the sky
看到天上的月亮
Introspect yourself well.
好好反省一下自己。
Why
为什么
are you looking down on me?
你是在看不起我吗？
You're almost a Japanese horse too.
你也快成了日本马了。
So you also have to introspect yourself
所以你也必须反省自己
even though Chen Jia Ping is very fierce towards me
尽管陈家平对我很凶
but he is a good person
但他是个好人
I really envy him.
我真的很羡慕他。
Amazed about what?
惊讶什么？
Become a hero.
成为英雄。
It definitely feels good.
感觉绝对不错。
Especially after becoming a hero and returning home,
尤其是成为英雄回国后，
there is still a beautiful wife who warms his blanket.
还有一个美丽的妻子为他暖被子。
Correct.
正确的。
Don't I still have you?
我心里还没有你吗？
Xiao Douzi.
Xiao Douzi.
The days ahead,
未来的日子，
we will both get through it.
我们都会渡过难关。
Wretched.
可怜。
The key was not in Xin Xuan's bag.
钥匙不在辛轩的包里。
Xiao Douzi.
Xiao Douzi.
We're about to leave.
我们正要离开。
Leave
离开
How about this?
这个怎么样？
Where can I get the key?
我在哪里可以获得钥匙？
Xiao Douzi, kembali
Xiao Douzi, kembali
return
返回
don't shoot.
别开枪。
Don't shoot
不要开枪
heart
心
what happened?
发生了什么？
Xiao Douzi.
Xiao Douzi.
Accordingly.
因此。
Lord under the mountain.
主在山下。
Lord under the mountain?
山下有主吗？
Owned by Han Lu.
属于韩露。
Here.
这里。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Two punctures.
两处刺伤。
Why are you here?
你为什么在这？
Sorry, everyone.
对不起，大家。
The horse was a little scared.
马有点害怕。
It doesn't hurt anything, right?
它不会伤害任何东西，对吧？
I ask you,
我问你，
why are you here?
你为什么在这？
I work here.
我在这儿上班。
This...
这...
Famous artist's wooden leg
著名艺术家的木腿
tuan Shan Xia
tuan Shan Xia
these two knives
这两把刀
has a bad habit of stealing women's things.
有偷女人东西的坏习惯。
Very fragrant.
很香。
Tuan Shan Xia.
Tuan Shan Xia.
Today is our big day.
今天是我们的大日子。
Don't shoot me, okay?
别开枪打我，好吗？